-Did you hear Sun lost a tennis match?
-I'd be so embarrassed.
-He's about to become a professional
athlete,
-and he lost to a nobody.
-So what if he lost to me?
-Thank you.
-You don't have to thank me.
-I'm going to have you play doubles.
-Sun asked you to do this, didn't he?
-You couldn't accept losing?
-Are you really an athlete?
-F*ck you!
-Next week, once both of you
have fully recovered,
-I’ll have Coach Kong hold another
tryout
-just for Sun and Bay.
-Didn't you say you were going
to withdraw?
-I wasn't going to withdraw
-because I thought I couldn't do it.
-I was going to withdraw
-so I wouldn't keep getting on your nerves.
-I'm sorry I punched you.
-Whoever's son loses,
-that family shuts down their shop.
-Huh?!
2. CONDITIONS OF DEFEAT
Mark my word,
if you lose and try to pull any tricks,
I'll see you in court.
Oh, please.
You’re the one who’s going to lose.
When you lose,
don't you dare cheat my son.
Pfft.
This place is so freaking old.
I'd better go.
It's called classic.
Not like your place.
Just a cheap copy.
Well, I'm proud of my "cheap copy."
It's a copy, but it's more delicious
than yours.
Oh, have you no shame?
When your shop closes down
and you're out of business,
come have a meal at my place.
Why would I go there?!
Your place is closing down soon!
Just get out of here!
Oh, you're up?
THAT FAMILY MUST SHUT DOWN
THEIR SHOP
Pa!
Pa, are you seriously doing this?
You will never lose to him anyway.
You know what?
This is a great opportunity
to get that family out of our sight.
Pa believes in you, son.
Dad!
Mom,
where's Dad?
He went somewhere.
He said he'd be back soon.
He left?
I guess so.
Oh, shit.
What "Oh, shit"?
Dad!
Yeah?
Have you signed the contract?
How did you find out?
How could I not?
Hey.
What?
What? Hey!
What contract?
Honey...
Whoever's son loses the tennis match,
that family must
shut down their shop,
including giving up the dim sum
business for life.
What have you done?!
Oh, Dad.
Honey, relax.
Hear me out.
This is our only chance
to make Chun stop messing with our family.
How could you do this
without talking to me first?
Hey, that's not necessary.
Bay beat Sun once.
He'll do it again.
Right, Bay?
Hey, you'll win again.
How could I beat him?
Hey! Be confident.
You already hate that boy, don't you?
Let's just seal the deal.
I don't hate him.
You don't?
It's not that.
I mean, Sun's shoulder has healed.
So now it'll be harder for me to win.
Just a little harder.
Didn't you tell me,
"If I think I can do it, I can do it.
I can do it"?
Oh, no reaction?
I was cheering for you, Bay.
Huh?
Let's just say
if you lose to Sun,
our family won't have the money
for you to study abroad.
Think of it this way.
You have to earn your victory
by defeating their son.
How did it come to this?
It is what it is.
-Going abroad?
-Bay.
If you win, which you definitely will
because you've beaten him once,
now you'll get to go study abroad.
SUPPORTED BY THE DEPARTMENT OF CULTURAL PROMOTION, MINISTRY OF CULTURE
Sun!
We need to talk.
What is there to talk about?
A lot, actually.
What are we going to do
about our dads?
Hey.
What?
Let go of my arm first.
What are we gonna do?
Follow me.
Okay.
Sun, I'm begging you.
If my family's shop goes out of business,
it's not just the shop.
I'll lose my chance to study abroad.
Huh?
Study abroad?
Yeah.
Because I won the match last time,
my dad let me go abroad.
But things have gotten out of hand.
Now everything's a mess.
You played against me
just because your dad dared you to?
Yeah, right!
That's it.
Should we find a way to void
the contract?
Or we could play to a draw.
-Please.
-Hey!
Please!
Please, I beg you.
Pretty please.
Whatever.
Hey, why?
If you want to go abroad,
then you'll just have to beat me.
Hey!
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
Oh, sh*t!
-Hey!
-Oh!
-Hey, I'm wet!
-Sh*t! My butt is wet!
How wet?
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, I'm all wet!
-Here, take this tissue.
-Oww!
Hey!
Let me.
Hey, stop!
I'll wipe it myself.
Sh*t! What if someone sees us like this?
Uh-oh.
Sorry, guys.
Please, go on.
Saturday, Sunday,
or last Sunday?
Last Friday night.
Oh, okay.
I was confused.
There are too many matches.
He's too good.
Sun's not here?
Oh.
Sun is resting his shoulder.
You're here to see Sun?
Hey.
No.
What about Coach Kong?
Coach Kong let us practice by ourselves.
Oh.
Umm...
Could somebody coach me?
Just someone.
Bay,
why do you want to practice?
Well, I...
I just think it's fun.
I want to improve my strokes.
Just tell me honestly.
No lies.
You want to beat Sun, don't you?
Yeah.
I can't lose.
Your form is already correct.
But when you're playing against Sun,
you need to hit the ball faster.
When you're returning,
don't step back past this cone.
You decided to coach me now?
Yeah, obviously.
What's up?
Sun, Bay asked us to help him practice.
Should I tell him to beat it?
Sun?
Did we lose him?
Ally, are you listening?
Yeah, what is it?
You should coach him.
You know his weaknesses, right?
Are you sure?
Mmm.
That's good.
Now he can't go home at
the same time as me.
SAMING PHON FAI
Pa!
My friend whom I met abroad
during a match came to visit.
So I'm going to meet him.
Oh...
Bring him some dim sum then.
Pa, it's all right.
Hold on a second.
No.
He's waiting for me.
It's okay.
They're already steamed.
Umm...
Hold on.
He's waiting for me.
It won't take long.
Bring it to your friend.
Yes, Pa.
Why did you bring all this?
I told Pa I was going to meet a friend,
so he made me bring this.
We're ready.
Hey, where's Mom?
She had to run some errands.
She can't be here today.
Oh.
But...
Mom told me to check on you.
See how you're doing after
getting punched.
She knows about this?
Of course.
Boy Excuse me,
who ordered this without carrots?
Here.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
And...
have you been punished?
Just cleaning the toilets.
Good. At least it's not that
big of a deal.
Are you okay?
Hey, bro.
Actually, there's something
I haven't told you.
There's a big problem.
You got it, right?
To go up against Sun,
you have to hit the ball that fast.
Even if you can keep up with his shots,
that doesn't mean you can beat Sun.
But I don't think Coach Kong assigning you
to doubles is a bad thing.
The way you play is actually
better suited for doubles.
Yeah, I did play doubles before.
Eh? Then why did you have such
a problem with it?
Just play doubles then.
No way.
Eww, your sweat!
Thanks for the coaching.
How much are these?
2,000 baht.
I'll scan to pay.
Here.
Normally, this would be serious
enough to get you fired.
But since this is your first offense,
your salary will be docked.
Umm, can you put these on hold?
I'll come get them later.
I can't. This is a rare item.
People are trying to get their hands on it.
Please.
Cut me some slack.
Can't you give me a discount?
I'll take this one.
Boat!
What are you doing here?
It's your money.
So now I don't have to pay you back, right?
Hey, hey, hey.
Didn't you borrow my money to buy this?
Think of it as your apology
for avoiding me.
Hey.
Are you really mad?
Huh?
I'm being serious.
Just answer me honestly.
Where have you been all these years?
Have you really been that busy?
Well... I'm here now.
Why are you so sensitive about it?
Are you really a teacher?
At least your little brother respects me.
He's just being polite.
By the way,
you don't look like a doctor at all.
Are you really studying medicine?
Why do you look like...
you don't take care of yourself?
And why did you come to see me?
Or did you just come to apologize?
Well...
there's a big problem.
Hey, dude!
Oh! What? What?
Are you going down?
Then why were you shouting?
Is it true
that your family and Sun's are betting
on the tennis match?
Huh?
The whole school is talking.
Is it true?
Just tell your best friend.
What?
Who started this rumor?
A high school tennis match
has turned into a business bet?
If the Principal finds out,
what's gonna happen?
I think
we should let the Principal know about this.
Huh?
No, we should let the students know first.
And when the Principal finds out,
she'll call off the match.
What's up, girl?
Huh!
Sun and Bay's families?
They're putting their dim sum shops
on a bet?
Don't let anyone know
that the match will be held at
the school field
on Monday at 6 p.m.
Where did you get this idea?
This plan...
I got the idea from an iconic old series.
Is it true?
Are your fathers making a bet?
PIRUNPORN CHUEAKAEWMANEE
It's not true.
I don't know why people are spreading
that rumor.
So it's not true,
isn't it?
Definitely not true.
I'm confused about this too.
My dad can be crazy,
but he's not actually that crazy.
Neither is mine.
However... from the looks of things,
there are probably going to be
a lot of students watching on match day.
It's bound to cause chaos.
Should we come up with another solution?
Coach Kong is right.
We were supposed to keep this quiet.
Isn't that right?
And if we postpone the match,
I don't think we'll be able to submit
the players' names in time.
So I think we should find another solution,
or just cancel the match altogether.
But now...
my shoulder has fully healed.
Should we...
hold the match this Friday instead?
-Huh?
Yeah, that's fine.
Are you okay with that, Bay?
Yes, ma'am. Perfect.
This Friday.
Let’s go see a doctor, Bay.
No, I’m okay.
I was just practicing in the sun
for too long.
Let’s see a doctor.
You’re still running a fever.
No, I’m not on my deathbed.
Look,
when it comes to someone you love,
you can’t help but worry
even over a slight sickness.
Umm.
Yes, Mom.
Go to sleep.
Good night, Mom.
GOT A FEVER RIGHT BEFORE THE MATCH
TWELVE BAKERY (PING)
What are you doing?
Is this for Bay?
Come on.
Don’t worry.
Come.
This is Bay’s room.
Go, get in.
Hurry, get in.
Just go.
Actually, you should give this to Bay.
You get in there.
Text me when you’re done.
I’ll keep watch outside.
Don’t worry.
Go, go.
Huh?
Hey!
Mmm, Mom?
Shhh.
What are you doing here?
Well, Boat posted a story of you
being sick.
When it comes to my business,
he overshares.
Are you okay?
You wanna put off the match?
I just have a heat fever.
You came all the way to my house?
You’re worried about me that much?
I’m not worried about you.
I’m just being a good sport.
Am I still running a fever?
Mmm.
You’re still hot.
Show me your forehead.
Do it for me.
You look just like my mom
when she wipes me down.
If you don’t feel better,
I’m not competing with you.
Is this you being a good sport again?
So if you lose,
you can’t use being sick as an excuse.
I still have…
a few more.
While I’m not here, put on a new one
so you can put up a good fight.
Or you’ll get completely beaten by me.
Go home, cocky.
Go to sleep.
MATCH DAY
The hell are you looking at?
Nothing.
Just checking if your shoulder is healed.
The match is about to begin
and you’re just asking me now?
Hey!
What is this?
Let me touch it.
Touch what?
What’s wrong with you?
Are you a doctor?
I’m not a doctor.
I just wanna touch it.
Does it hurt here?
I told you it doesn’t hurt anymore.
Mmm.
Okay.
I can still remember, too.
Hmm?
What?
Nothing.
See you at the court.
Sh*t, damn it!
I knew it!
(I can still remember, too.)
What’s the point of telling me now?
Bay.
Dad.
Good evening.
Hi.
Good evening. Good evening.
You’re late and still acting like it’s nothing.
Hmph!
What, Chun?
How am I late?
They said 1 p.m. and I arrived at 1 p.m.
Hey.
A well-mannered person should arrive
a little early.
And more importantly,
today is your son’s big day.
As his father, you should know
how to behave.
Oh, what a well-mannered guy.
Let me tell you,
I had tons of orders at the shop,
and I’m a father.
I know that…
-Making money for the family…
-Let’s go, honey.
-is the most important thing.
-That’s enough, honey.
-Not like you. Your shop…
-Let’s go find our seats.
How many shumai can your shop
even sell in a day?
Damn.
Just excuses.
You tried your best.
It is what it is.
Can we start, Coach Kong?
All right, sir.
Umm…
Bay, you’re ready?
I’m ready.
And Sun?
Just a sec, Coach.
If it’s too much, you can tell me.
They’re here!
Mom!
Hello, Pa.
Hello.
I know about all of this.
I’m here to support you.
Do your best.
Yes, Mom.
Even if you lose, it’s okay.
If the shop closes,
you can come live with me.
Heads or tails?
Heads.
So you’re tails?
Choose.
I’ll serve.
I’ll take this court.
Go!
Go, go, Sun!
GREAT SWING, GREAT SCORES
Go, Sun, go, Sun!!
SAMING PHON FAI
ALL SUPERIOR!
Go, Bay, go.
SWING HARD! SHOW THEM
WHAT MERLION CAN DO!
Let’s do this.
Go, go, go.
Sun, go, Sun!!
Sun, go, Sun.
Yay!!
Again.
That’s it.
You got this.
Yeah!
Yes!
GREAT SWING, GREAT SCORES
SAMING PHON FAI
ALL SUPERIOR!
Yay!!
It’s okay, Bay.
Try again.
Relax. Focus.
Yay!!
Amazing!
Damn it.
Yes!
Yay!!
That’s amazing, Bay!
-Woo!
-Yay!
That’s my boy.
I’m so back.
Show them what we’re made of, Bay.
What are you so happy about, huh?
It’s just one score.
The first point on the road
to your downfall, Chun!!
Honey.
Okay, honey, okay.
Sun, go, Sun!!
Let’s go!!
Yay!!
Amazing!!
That’s it! How about that?!
Yes!
It’s okay, Bay. It’s okay.
It’s just the first set.
GREAT SWING, GREAT SCORES
SAMING PHON FAI
ALL SUPERIOR!
Take this.
You did well.
Boat, go check on him.
Don’t make me come down there.
Okay, Dad.
Well done, Sun.
Just keep your focus.
The opponent will eventually get tired.
Are you okay?
Just relax.
Breathe in and out slowly.
Drink some water.
Don’t worry.
If you lose, that’s fine.
I’ll talk to Dad and Mom.
You’ll get to study abroad anyway.
I’m not really afraid of him.
Besides,
I’m starting to figure out his game too.
Good.
Here.
Have some water.
Thank you.
Ready?
Ready.
-Get ready.
-Yes.
If you’re ready, let’s continue.
Ready?
You got this?
Yes, Pa.
Do your best.
Go!
Go, Sun.
Concentrate.
Yes!!
Good.
It’s been almost an hour.
Game.
Tie-break.
SWING HARD! SHOW THEM
WHAT MERLION CAN DO!
GREAT SWING, GREAT SCORES
SAMING PHON FAI
ALL SUPERIOR!
Oww! Sht.
Yes!
Great job, Bay.
That’s my son.
See?
Oww.
Woo!
Hold this.
I’ll check on him.
How is it?
Are you okay?
I think so.
What?
Is there something wrong,
Coach Kong?
Umm,
it’s getting late now.
And they’ve been playing for so long.
So I think
we should put this on pause
and continue another day?
Hey.
Eh?
We’re in the middle of the match?
Why are we stopping now?
Huh?
They’re in a flow.
Just let them play.
Yeah.
Besides,
I don’t have time to come watch
another game.
I have a business to run.
Look, Coach Kong,
Sun has done this before.
He’s been in a match that was
longer than this.
Umm, but…
this match is different.
I mean…
What?
Oh, well…
they both seem more exhausted
than they usually do.
So I think they should have some rest.
Huh?
Isn’t this normal?
Sun, are you okay?
Yes, Pa.
Yeah.
He said he’s okay.
What about you, Bay?
I’m fine.
You’re sure?
-Yes, Coach.
Okay.
Then… let’s continue.
Okay, go.
Give it your best shot.
Go, go.
Get him.
Go, go, go, go.
Fault!
Wow.
Hey, are you all right?
Bay,
you okay?
I’m okay.
Sun, go, Sun!
Yeah!
Good.
Come on.
Hang in there.
Concentrate.
That’s right.
SAMING PHON FAI
Ahem.
Hey!
Hang on.
What do you want now?
Thank you.
For what?
Oh, please.
Don’t act nonchalant.
Bring it.
Sh*t.
What if he sees us?
What if my dad sees us?
You’ll make me stink too.
Go, go!
You’re back?
How was your meeting with your friends?
It was fine, Dad.
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Where did you go?
Why do you smell musty?
Umm…
Oh,
I stopped to play with a dog.
What dog?
You wanna keep a dog?
Oh, no.
No, Dad.
It was just a stray dog.
(Stray dog?)
It was cute.
Hey, wait!
Don’t get on the bed in that outfit.
You’ll make the bed smell.
Yes, Pa.
SAMING PHON FAI
-Bay!
-Do you realize you’re acting
super weird?
-How?
-Well, you…
-You act like you care about me.
-Just answer me.
-Why did you hug me?
-The question you asked me,
-I’d like to know the answer too.
SUPPORTED BY THE DEPARTMENT OF CULTURAL PROMOTION, MINISTRY OF CULTURE